Succubus is a horror, thriller film directed by R.J. Daniel Hanna.
A new father going through a marital separation joins a dating app and
matches with a beautiful but mysterious young woman...
whose powers of seduction and manipulation entangle him in a mystery
more horrifying than he could have ever imagined.
Chris, played by Brendan Bradley.
Adra, played by Rachel Cook.
Sharon, played by Olivia Grace Applegate.
Eddie, played by Derek Smith.
Charlisse, played by Emily Kincaid.
Dr. Orion Zephyr, played by Ron Perlman.
Succubus (German: Necronomicon – Geträumte Sünden, lit.
'Necronomicon – Sinful Dreams') is a 1968 West German erotic horror film directed by Jesús
Franco and starring Janine Reynaud, Jack Taylor, Adrian Hoven, and Michel Lemoine.
It follows Lorna Green, a performer at a Lisbon nightclub who performs
fictionalized acts that involve erotically charged sadomasochistic murders.
As she begins to suffer violent, surreal nightmares, it is suggested that Lorna
may be under mind control by a man who may be Satan incarnate.
Succubus was Franco's first film made entirely outside of Spain.
During production, the German backers for the film fell out,
leading to the producer contacting Pier A.
Caminnecci to finance the film.
The film was released in West Germany in April 1968, and was subsequently acquired by American
International Pictures, who distributed it in the United States beginning in April 1969.
The tone is dark and intense.